Don't fit in. Stand out.
Camp Rock is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Matthew Diamond.
When Mitchie gets a chance to attend Camp Rock, her life takes an unpredictable
twist, and she learns just how important it is to be true to yourself.
Mitchie Torres, played by Demi Lovato.
Shane Gray, played by Joe Jonas.
Tess Tyler, played by Meaghan Jette Martin.
Connie Torres, played by Maria Canals-Barrera.
Caitlyn Geller, played by Alyson Stoner.
Dee La Duke, played by Julie Brown.
Camp Rock is a 2008 musical television film directed by Matthew Diamond from a
screenplay by Karin Gist, Regina Hicks, Julie Brown, and Paul Brown.
The 73rd Disney Channel Original Movie (DCOM), the film stars Demi Lovato, Joe Jonas,
Meaghan Jette Martin, Maria Canals-Barrera, Daniel Fathers, and Alyson Stoner.
In the film, aspiring teenage singer Mitchie Torres
(Lovato) visits Camp Rock, a summer music camp.
The film premiered on Disney Channel on June 20, 2008.
Camp Rock was the second DCOM to air on ABC's The Wonderful World of Disney after its premiere on Disney
Channel and was placed on the iTunes Store for digital purchase shortly after its premiere.
The film was watched by 8.9 million viewers on the night of its premiere and is currently the third highest
viewed DCOM of all time, behind High School Musical 2 and Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie.
A sequel, Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam, premiered on September 3, 2010.
The film explores themes of summer camp, rock
star, aspiring singer, camp, singing.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.